The radiance of the night shines through my window
but the path to immortality is long.
The Eight Views and Nine-Bend Streams are desolate.
Living beings question the miseries of the world over a jar of wine.
Forget about Nirvana and rebirth,
I will break through the waves with my own flesh and blood.
The heavens are vast, so what if I was born mediocre ?
I stare at the Dao in my moments of madness
as the storm rages just below.
I've been thinking about life and death in my dreams.
I've unsheathed my sword to ask the immortals
why the world is a-changing.
Heaven and earth reveals its poignant truths.
Swallow the Four Seas and the Eight Wastelands,
experience all the vicissitudes of life in an instant.
I will defy the light in the sky
to continue to write a new chapter for all things in the three realms of existence.
Just a thought separates mortal from immortal.
Transform your insignificant body into light.
The hardships of the journey
will temper this young man's heart.
If I become a Renegade Immortal, will I hesitate to fight the heavens ?
Renegade Immortal
Subtitles by Bonobosubs
https://discord.gg/Ceckd4pdVA
Sea of Devils
It's said that many Spirit Beasts live in the Sea of Devils.
Most cultivators here don't follow common sense
and only value strength...
Also...
there are very few women.
Once a woman is discovered,
terrible things will happen to her
unless she has powerful backing.
She is mine !
Senior !
Come out !
How dare you !
Middle stage Foundation Establishment ?
There are 3 of them !
Senior,
let's retreat.
Brat,
this is the territory of the Fighting Evil Sect.
If you're smart,
then leave that female to us.
Otherwise...
Nonsense... Die !
They...
How ?
Didn't you say that cultivators here don't follow reason
and only value strength ?
What you just used...
was it the Death Spell ?
The Death Spell ?
I once read in the Luo River Sect's scripture pavilion
that a vicious spell
of the demonic path existed in ancient times.
Cultivating it
required merging 3 energies.
The first energy was yin energy
by using a woman's Primordial Yin
Note: Primordial Yin = virginity
through dual cultivation.
The second energy was death energy.
The third was killing intent.
Merge these 3 energies
and escape death 9 times
to master the Death Spell.
The chance of succeeding
is almost zero.
It's really similar...
This Death Spell
is likely an imitation of the Ji Realm.
It's perfect for concealing the Ji Realm's existence.
Once the Heaven Separating Pill is refined
and I reach Core Formation,
I will let you leave.
But if you think of escaping...
don't blame me !
This guy
is even more terrifying than cultivators of the Sea of Devils.
An abandoned cave ?
The mountains in the Sea of Devils
are hard to excavate.
Let's find another place.
His Divine Sense
can control over 30 flying swords simultaneously !
This formation is pretty ordinary.
It can only resist Foundation Establishment cultivators.
I plan to stay in this cave long-term.
If the formation is broken,
I can easily escape.
But you will have to rely on yourself.
Note: The Eight Chinese Trigrams have various different meanings in Feng Shui.
Qian: Triple lines
Kun: Six fragments
Zhen: Upside bowl
Gen: Downside bowl
Li: Hollow bowl
Kan: Full bowl
Dui: Open top
Xun: Open bottom
3 hours later
There are now 214 formations.
I used bones of crystal beasts
to make the Nine Bones Formation.
The formation is only at 30% power.
To make it stronger,
we need more bones.
You first...
Judging by this cave's condition,
a cultivator was here before us.
Senior,
should I refine the Heaven Separating Pill now ?
I won't consume
the pills you make.
Senior saved my life.
How can I earn your trust ?
You need to give me your Soul Blood.
But I won't make it too difficult for you.
Just refine enough pills for me
to reach Core Formation.
Once I'm done,
I'll escort you out of the Sea of Devils.
Here are the materials I have,
see what you can refine with that.
This...
this is Desolate Wood Root,
and Yellow Core Grass...
Heaven Spirit Grass !
Senior,
I can freely use all these materials ?
Right ?
I only want pills.
As for the process,
you can do whatever you wish.
Senior can rest assured.
With these materials,
I can refine
approximately 300 Yellow Spirit Pills,
50 Poison Resistance Pills,
and various other pills.
Senior,
look at this Demon Blood Vine.
It used to be the core ingredient of the Heaven Separating Pill.
However,
refining the pills will take considerable time.
The Nine Bones Formation
probably won't last that long.
I plan on making a trip outside
to look for more bones for the formation.
I'll come back
in 3 days, maybe a week.
The artifact crafting technique of the War God Shrine
also requires Spirit Beast skulls for reaction furnaces.
Senior...
Could you
also find me a pill furnace ?
The pill furnace I carry can only refine ordinary pills.
Usually, Heaven Separating Pills
were refined in the sect's Heaven Fusing Furnace.
According to the map,
I should be able to find bones around here.
Sang Muya
Fighting Evil Sect disciple
15th layer of Qi Condensation
I painstakingly prepared
these 16 deadly poisons.
Senior Brother,
you're not young anymore.
why don't you help your Junior Brother
by letting me use Foundation Stealing
to devour you !
Sang Muya,
you bastard !
aren't you afraid of Master ?
I'm just following the tradition
of the Fighting Evil Sect.
Master has already tacitly approved.
I had my Divine Sense
spread out to scan the area
but I didn't detect him...
Junior Sang Muya of the Fighting Evil Sect
greets Senior.
I didn't know Senior was here,
how can I help you ?
Where did you
find your beast bones ?
Senior,
we were in the outskirts of the Sea of Devils.
I'm taking you
to a more central area
were there are more Spirit Beasts
and thus more bones.
He probably isn't lying.
Senior,
the Sea of Devils
has 3 very dangerous areas.
This Corpse Valley
is one of them.
Spirit beasts often come here.
New corpses of beasts are found here regularly.
But we don't know
what killed them.
This must be the place.
Now die !
There are hundreds of souls in that flag.
I guess I can feed them to Xu Liguo.
The quality of the bones is too poor.
I guess I need to explore a bit more.
Even if the bones here aren't top quality,
they can still strengthen
the Nine Bones Formation.
It seems like yin energy is gathering here too.
This valley
is completely different from the previous one.
Although it appears calm,
it's one of the most dangerous places
in the Sea of Devils.
There must be some kind of danger here.
This is...
a Flood Dragon !
This Flood Dragon
is probably even stronger
than a Nascent Soul cultivator.
You're mine !
10 days later
He said 3 days
but it's already been 10...
Open the formation.
Will the bones
of this Flood Dragon be enough
for the formation ?
Yes.
With Flood Dragon bones
the formation
will resist Core Formation cultivators for days.
Even Nascent Soul cultivators will struggle.
This formation
can't be called the Nine Bones Formation anymore.
It should be...
the Nine Dragon Bones Formation !
Wait.
These are the Flood Dragon's Core and marrow.
The Core is a natural pill
and has healing properties.
The marrow is even more precious,
it's concentrated spiritual energy.
You can
leave the rest to me.
Grade 2
Earth Yin
Although it can't compare to
the Grade 4 Earth Yin in the Corpse Valley,
it's enough to cultivate.
the Underworld Ascension Method.
Now,
I need to prepare for Core Formation.
My second Cold Core condensed.
We'll see where you run off to this time.
I'm going out.
Senior, wait.
The Sea of Devils is dangerous
and Flood Dragon skin is resistant
and poison-proof.
I took the liberty of crafting it
so that Senior
may use it.
If Senior still doubts me,
you can throw it outside the cave
to strengthen the formation.
I just need one,
keep the other.
3 months later
Little Lin
The Ancestral meridian,
the Qi Sea
and the Dantian
will each condense a Cold Core.
The Underworld Ascension Method merges the 3 Cold Cores.
After they've merged,
you have a chance to breakthrough to Core Formation
by forming your true Golden Core.
I still can't merge the Cold Cores...
I need to try harder.
Damn it !
Master, oh Master...
Normally, I can only appear when summoned.
But now that you're unconscious,
it seems my chance for freedom has finally come !
I've been walking this path for endless years
just to catch a glimpse of your silhouette.
Is it the compass of fate
that wrote this outcome for us ?
The heavens want to erase your existence,
that's the obsession guiding me.
Is this the path to uncover
truths from falsehoods ?
In a world of murk and shadow,
only the flame of truth can light the way.
Look at them all,
being carried by the waves.
being drowned.
I don't want to believe in whoever decides fate,
I will let the world refine my soul.
So what if I become an Immortal and defy the heavens ?
I will fight.
I'll break through the abyss of despair
to finally learn who I really am.
My body is stained by the bloody color of slaughter,
I embrace this obsession.
I won't glance back at the wasteland I left behind.
Even if this suffering shatters my soul
and I'm reborn countless times in hell,
I'll still fight.
It's hard to avoid loneliness
when you are above everyone else.
Can a moth that has witnessed the flames of a Suzaku
be afraid of a firefly ?